just for the record have you ever been
in this van before no do you think that
you could live here with that little kid
I think so cuz we wouldn't be in here
but sleeping the more you focus on the
outdoors the less indoors matters well
yeah people always say you can't do this
with kids but you're actually in the van
that I live in do you think you could
live in this thing fulltime with a child
yeah I feel like we use as long as we
were places you know where he had the
outdoor access where you could spend the
time with him running around that energy
outside and also just so you understand
we rarely use the toilet in here rarely
use the shower you always shower and
usually in a river or at a Planet
Fitness if you want to or at a friend's
house too sometimes all you need to take
a shower is a hose and a bar of soap or
a bucket in some go running water some
nice cold water but feasible for two
people with a child in just a a van yeah
definitely yeah just a van first time
seeing El Suave hey once you see
something this red you can't unsee it oh
yeah hey you like this kid cool yeah
yeah could you live in this yeah am I
cool yeah yeah yeah awesome man hey
welcome to the van dude can you say
elave all close enough kid close enough
you're
in